As a small business owner, we know how
difficult it is to run a business.
Whether you are low on cash, needing new
equipment, requiring a steady cash flow,
or looking
to obtain working capital, a merchant cash
advance
is an easy solution to get working capital
for your business.
Unlike traditional bank loans, merchant
cash advance is
a purchase of business future receivables.
At GLD Funding, we provide quick access to
funds in only 24 hours.
We utilize your expected future sales to
be
able to provide you with working capital
for
your business needs.
Why choose GLD Funding?
We offer quick approvals, flexible
repayment options,
minimal paperwork, and no minimum credit
score required.
Overall, simple and fast funding.
It's quick and easy.
Fill out an application with your basic
information.
Once filled out, submit along with your
last
three months of your business bank
statements.
Our underwriting team will review your
application and
financial statements to develop a solution
specific to
your business needs.
One of our funding specialists will
contact you
with an offer.
There are no personal guarantees and
minimal documents required.
Once contracts signed, you will receive
your funds
and your bank account on the same day.
What are you waiting for?
Call us today.
Follow us on Instagram and Facebook or
visit our website.